Let there be blood.
Johnny & Clyde is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Tom DeNucci.
Johnny and Clyde are two serial killers who are madly
in love and on an endless crime spree.
Alana (Megan Fox) is the confident and cunning owner of a prosperous
casino that generates tens of millions of dollars each year.
Johnny and Clyde decide to assemble a ragtag group of criminals and misfits to
steal from Alana's casino and pull off the heist of the century.
Unfortunately for Johnny and Clyde's crew, Alana has a deadly weapon at her
disposal – the monstrous slasher spirit known as Bakwas.
Johnny, played by Avan Jogia.
Clyde, played by Ajani Russell.
Alana Hart, played by Megan Fox.
Guy, played by Tyson Ritter.
Susan, played by Vanessa Angel.
Pot, played by Sydney Jenkins.
Johnny & Clyde is a 2023 American horror-heist film directed by
Tom DeNucci, who co-wrote it with Nick Principe.
The film stars Megan Fox, Avan Jogia, and Ajani Russell.
The plot follows a pair of serial killers who assemble a team to rob a
casino but become hunted by a demon guarding the cash room.
The film received a 0% rating on Rotten Tomatoes and was nominated for two
Golden Raspberry Awards, with Fox winning for Worst Actress.
The tone is intense.